# Scott Gangemi

### Hey there,

I'm Scott. I'm a software engineer and I'm passionate about building cool applications, and seeing the impact of awesome work.

My favourite thing about software development is creating fantastic experiences that people will love, and want to keep coming back to.





**Call me** 0431 987 232



or don't.

s.gangemi@me.com



scottgangemi.com github.com/Gangezilla

### Experience

### Expert360 Jul 2018 - Now Software Developer

- Building React components for our platform, as well as building a significant portion of our design system.
- Building new features for our platform in current, and legacy servers.

#### APG & Co. 2016 - 2017 Junior Web Developer

Some of my teams favourite accomplishments were:

- Redesigned our bloated six page checkout into a sleek one page wonder.
- Tore out all of our old CSS and converted it to SASS (cutting off 300kb in the process).
- Rewrote thousands of lines of mystery JavaScript into easy to understand React.

#### Domain Apr 2017 - Jul 2018 Full Stack JavaScript Developer

- Built React components and Node Servers, as well as optimising performance for them.
- Rebuilt Domain's listings pages and transitioned them away from a legacy monolith code base.

## Volunteering

#### **NodeGirls**

I've mentored and taught at NodeGirls a number of times and have:

- Mentored individuals in an Express class.
- Helped to organise and run a React workshop.

### **Education**

#### **UTS**

2012 - 2015

Bachelor of Integrated Product Design: Major in Interaction Design

#### **Skills**

I'm really comfortable with:

- Building performant React apps
- Anything JavaScript and CSS
- ElixirGraphQL

I'm currently learning:

- Databases
  Networking
- Computer Science fundamentals
- Architecture of applications